bureauveritas.com 2008-12-16

# PRIVACY POLICY

**We regard your privacy as being of primary importance. Any information which we collect from you, when you chose to provide it to us, is to enable us to send you information about products and services in which you register an interest.**

Information may be provided to other companies within Bureau Veritas for this purpose. By providing us with your information you consent to us processing it for the purposes outlined above. We will not pass it on to any third party outside Bureau Veritas, except to fulfil our orders or to supply a request.

Below you can find more detailed information concerning the policy of Bureau Veritas websites.

 **Browsing the website** **  
**When you visit any site registered and operated by **Bureau Veritas** to browse the information it contains, you do so anonymously _unless_ you choose to provide us with information about yourself. 

If you do nothing during your visit apart from browse through the website, for example reading pages, viewing images, or downloading information without submitting any personal information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally.

Information gathered automatically is used for only two purposes: site management and, in the case of suspected unauthorised activity, law enforcement and possible criminal prosecution (See the Security Notice under “Terms of Use”).

The Bureau Veritas websites automatically log visitor information from which summary statistics are created. 

We use summary statistics to help us make our site more useful to visitors, such as assessing what information is of most and least interest to visitors, and for other purposes such as determining the site's technical design specifications and identifying system performance or problem areas.

The following are representative of the types of information automatically collected and stored about your visit:

·        the Internet domain and Internet Protocol (IP) address from which you access our website 

·        the type of Internet browser and the operating system of the computer you use to access our site

·            the date and time you visit our site 

·        the pages you visit our site

·        if you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website

·        if you linked to our website from a search website, the address of that website and the search term you used.

 **Sending e-mails to** **Bureau Veritas via Bureau Veritas websites  
**If you choose to submit a question or comment by e-mail, and provide us with your name and e-mail or postal address, we will use that information only to respond to your question or comment and to make contact with you with regard to the services on our site for which you have expressed interest.

Unless you indicate otherwise, we collect your information only for the purpose of answering your question or dealing with your comment and to enable Bureau Veritas to contact you with regard to the services on our site for which you have expressed interest.

We will not share your name, e-mail, or postal address with any third party, other than as described in our Security Notice under “Terms of Use”.

Under no circumstances will we give your name, e-mail, or postal address to any private organisation, commercial or otherwise, except to fulfil our orders or to supply a request.

 **Completing forms and downloading information on the BUREAU VERITAS websites**  
If you choose to provide us with information via a form, or to download information on Bureau Veritas websites, we will use that information only to complete the request specified by that form and to make contact with you with regard to the services on our site for which you have expressed interest. ****

If you choose to complete any Bureau Veritas form, we will collect your information by an automated process.

Unless you indicate otherwise on the form we collect your information only for the purpose of completing the request you have specified and to enable Bureau Veritas to contact you with regard to the services on our site for which you have expressed interest.

We will not share your information with any third party, other than as described in our Security Notice under “Terms of Use”.

Unless otherwise specifically stated on a particular form, we will under no circumstances give your information to any private organisation, commercial or otherwise, except to fulfil our orders or to supply a request.

We will retain the information provided by you only for so long as is reasonably appropriate under the applicable legislation.

 **Security  
** This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. All of our users' information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100 % secure. Accordingly, despite our efforts to protect your personal information Bureau Veritas cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, or to or from our online products or services. You transmit all such information at your own risk. However, once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

Bureau Veritas' policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond Bureau Veritas' control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation.

 **Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

 **Contact Details**  
Corporate Communication Department manages the overall corporate information content, design and organisation of Bureau Veritas website. 

If you have any questions or comments about the information presented here, please contact Bureau Veritas Corporate Communication Department at the following address:

 **Bureau Veritas  
Corporate Communications Department  
17 bis, Place des Reflets  
La Défense 2  
92400 Courbevoie  
France** ****
